slicktext.com 2019-09-13

# Our Privacy Policy | SlickText

SlickText.com (the "Website") is a text message product that enables clients of Slick Innovations, LLC ("SlickText", "we", "us", "our") to send and receive communications with their customers via short message service ("SMS"). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy").

This Privacy Policy is entered into by and between you and SlickText. This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the Website, and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.

## Acceptance of the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use

This Privacy Policy is effective with respect to any data that we've collected, or collect, about and/or from you, according to our terms of use, found at https://www.slicktext.com/termsofuse.php (the "Terms of Use"), which is incorporated herein by reference. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully before you start to use the Website or our products and services. By using the Website or by clicking to accept or agree to the Terms of Use when this option is made available to you, you accept and agree to be bound and abide by this Privacy Policy. If you do not want to agree to the Terms of Use or this Privacy Policy, you must not access or use the Website or our products and services.

## Contact Information

If you have any questions or comments, or if you want to update, delete, or change any personal information we hold, or you have a concern about the way in which we have handled any privacy matter, please contact us at: Slick Innovations, LLC 301 E 2nd St #304 Jamestown, NY 14701; through our website; or at (800) 688-6290

## Information We Collect From You

We collect several types of information from and about our Website users including, but not limited to:

  * Information by which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, email address, telephone number, social security number, credit card information, and/or any other identifier by which you may be contacted online or offline ("personal information");
  * Information that is about you, but individually does not identify you, such as industry information; and/or
  * Information about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website, and usage details.

## How We Collect Information From You

We collect information from you in the following ways:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us;
  * Automatically as you navigate through the Website (for example, usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies; and
  * From our account holders about their users that opt in to a text messaging list.

## How We Use Information We Collect From You

We use information we collect from you or that your provide to us, including, but not limited to, any personal information, in the following ways:

  * To present our Website and its contents to you;
  * To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us;
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it; and/or
  * To set up your user account.

If credit card information is provided to us, this information is sent to a third party payment processor for the sole purpose of processing payments for our products or services that you order, and credit card information is not stored in our systems;

If a social security or tax identification number is provided to us, we use this information for the sole purpose of processing and sending you tax forms related to the use of our products and services (It is the policy of SlickText to protect the confidentiality of social security numbers, prohibit unlawful disclosure of social security numbers, and to limit access to social security numbers to those employees that require such access to process tax forms in accordance with this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.);

Our Website account holders may automatically be subscribed to our email newsletter as part of the account setup process. All individuals have the opportunity to choose to opt-out from receiving our newsletter or other non-account related emails, either during the account creation process or through opt-out instructions that are provided in our email or SMS communications. Your personal information will not be shared or distributed with third parties for marketing or advertising purposes.

We maintain log files tracking IP addresses to analyze trends, help diagnose problems with our servers, and to monitor traffic/usage in order to provide better service to our Website users and visitors. IP addresses are not used by us to personally identify individuals, and we do not link IP addresses to other forms of identifiable information, however IP addresses may be considered to be personal information under the laws of certain jurisdictions;

The ownership of any information communicated to SlickText for text messaging and/or storage purposes will remain with the user, and we will store such information securely in accordance with our security policy and the law.

We will not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to any third party unless we have your consent to do so or as otherwise disclosed in this Privacy Policy. We will only use and/or disclose personal information in order to: provide you with any services that you have engaged us for; understand and meet your needs and preferences; develop new and enhance existing service and product offerings; manage and develop our business and operations; comply with obligations resulting from a sale of all or substantially all of our assets; and meet legal and regulatory requirements.

We also reserve the right to use aggregated data, provided that the data is not linked to any specific individual, to help improve our products and services. Except where we are required by law to disclose personal information, we will use reasonable efforts to require any person to whom we provide your personal information to agree to comply with our then current Privacy Policy. However, to the extent allowed under applicable law, we will have no liability to you if any person fails to do so.

To be able to serve you, your personal information may be collected, stored, and/or processed or otherwise used by or on our behalf both inside and outside of Canada and the United States by third party service providers, to perform cloud storage, payment processing and other functions on our behalf. As a result, those country's courts, governments or law enforcement agencies could obtain disclosure of such information under such country's laws.

## Individual Choice and Access

We do our best to keep your data accurate and up to date, to the extent that you provide us with the information we need to do that. If your data changes (like a new email address or phone number), then you're responsible for notifying us of those changes.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as long as needed to provide you with the products or services that you have requested. We may also retain and use your information in order to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, prevent abuse, and enforce our agreements. It is SlickText's policy to delete personal information about account holders and their users when their account is no longer active.

We will provide an individual access to any personal information we hold about them within thirty (30) days of any request for that information. Individuals may request this information from us by contacting us using the contact information provided above. Unless it is prohibited by law, we will remove any personal information about an individual from our servers at their request. There is no charge for an individual to access or update his or her personal information.

It is SlickText's policy that, just as a user must opt in to a text messaging list, they have the right to opt out of a particular text messaging list as well. When a user opts out of a text messaging list, they will no longer receive any texts from that particular list unless they, themselves, re-subscribe. SlickText is not responsible for the text or picture messages sent by our clients or customers that are using SlickText products or services. It is the sole responsibility of the SlickText clients to acquire proper permission to send text messages and/or MMS messages to their subscribers.

Users can remove themselves from any client's SMS list at any time by texting "stop" along with the textword they signed up for. Reply "stop all" to remove your number from all of SlickText's client's lists.

## Anti-Spam Policy

SlickText requires its users to adhere to the Mobile Marketing Association's most current version of the policy document U.S. Consumer Best Practices for Messaging, found at http://www.mmaglobal.com/documents/us-consumer-best-practices, in addition to the CTIA Short Code Monitoring Handbook, which can be accessed through https://www.ctia.org/about-ctia/programs. Unsolicited messages, or any messages sent by unauthorized users of SlickText's products and services, are not tolerated by SlickText and are considered spam. Please review our anti-spam policy located at https://www.slicktext.com/antispam.php for more information regarding the reporting of suspected spam to SlickText.

## Cookie Policy

We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to improve the convenience and efficiency of your experience when using our products and services. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive tied to statistical information about the user. Usage of a cookie may be linked to an IP address of the user, but is not otherwise linked to any personally identifiable information in our services and email messages.

We may also use tracking pixels (also known as clear gifs or web beacons), which are invisible 1x1 pixel images that are requested from a remote server via a url that typically contains small strings of encoded information, which may in part be determined by cookies. When a tracking pixel is requested from a server, that server may decode and process this information, for example, storing it to server log files for future analysis.

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers or tracking utility companies) may use cookies on our Website. We do not have access or control over these cookies. For example, our Website utilizes Google Analytics, a common website analytics tool. For more information about Google Analytics, please refer to the website, "How Google uses data when you use our partners' sites or apps" at http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/.

Our Website also utilizes Google AdSense, a common web advertising service. Google AdSense uses cookies that are stored on your computer and allow an analysis of the use of the Website by you. Google AdSense also uses web beacons to gather information. Through the use of web beacons, simple actions such as visitor traffic to the Website can be recorded and collected. The information generated by the Google AdSense cookies and/or web beacons store information about your use of this Website, including your IP address. Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the Website in order to show you relevant advertisements, compile reports on Website activity and ads for Website operators, and provide other internet related services. Users may opt out of personalized Google advertising by visiting https://www.google.com/settings/ads/. 

Our Website may use Facebook pixels, which help us track conversions from Facebook ads, optimize ads based on collected data, build targeted audiences for future ads, and remarket to qualified leads.

This site uses the following categories of cookies:

  * Strictly necessary cookies - these are cookies that are required for the operation of our website. They include, for example, a first part session-id, which identifies a user and stores the application servers to use for the user's session.
  * Analytics & customization cookies - these functional cookies collect information that is used either in aggregate form to help us understand how our websites are being used or how effective our marketing campaigns are, or to help us customize our websites and applications for you in order to enhance your experience.
  * Performance & functionality cookies - these cookies are used to enhance the performance and functionality of our website but are non-essential to their use. However, without these cookies, certain functionality may become unavailable.
  * You can always choose to not accept cookies, but you may not be able to use some of the Website services. Users may visit the websites of those vendors listed above to opt out of the use of cookies for personalized advertising (if the vendor or ad network offers this capability). 

Alternatively, users may opt out of some third-party vendors' uses of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting http://www.aboutads.info/. Please use the following link to help you opt out of any remarketing pixels and related technologies: http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/.

## Online Tracking / Do Not Track

We do not track our visitors across third party websites to provide targeted advertising and therefore we do not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals. However, some third party sites do keep track of your browsing activities when they serve you content, which enables them to tailor what they present to you. If you are visiting such sites, your internet browser may allow you to set the DNT signal on your browser so that third parties (particularly advertisers) know you do not want to be tracked.

## No Collection of Children's Personal Information

This Website is intended for audiences at least 18 years old. We do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. We reserve the right to delete any information we believe to be in violation of this Privacy Policy.

## Security

If a security breach causes an unauthorized intrusion into our system that materially affects you, then we will promptly notify you in accordance with applicable legal requirements.

## Other Web Sites; Links

Our Website may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Third parties may independently collect information about you when you view communications from third parties through our products or services. If you do not want those companies to collect information about you, please contact them directly.

## Social Media Platforms

Our Website includes social media features, such as links to our Facebook or Twitter pages. These features may collect information about your IP address and which page you're visiting on our Website, and they may set a cookie to make sure the feature functions properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. We also maintain presences on social media platforms like Facebook, Twitter, and Pinterest. Any information, communications, or materials you submit to us via a social media platform is done at your own risk without any expectation of privacy. We cannot control the actions of other users of these platforms or the actions of the platforms themselves. Your interactions with those features and platforms are governed by the privacy policies of the companies that provide them.

## No Liability

You understand that electronic communications may be accessed by unauthorized parties when communicated across the Internet, network communications facilities, or other electronic means. You agree that we are not responsible for any electronic communication and/or any of your data which may be lost, altered, intercepted or stored without authorization during the transmission of any data whatsoever across networks not owned and/or operated by us. We do not guarantee that your information will not be misused or disclosed to third parties. We will not have any liability to you for any such misuse or disclosure.

## Consent

By using the Website and our products or services, you consent to the collection and use of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. Except as required or allowed by law, we will not use or disclose your personal information for any purpose for which you refuse us consent or later withdraw your consent. If you withdraw consent, you agree that in spite of this withdrawal we may continue to use the personal information previously provided to us to the extent that we are legally or contractually obligated to do so and to the extent necessary to enforce any contractual obligations you may have to us. You also understand that although you can use our Website for some purposes without providing us with any personal information, we need personal information about you for some products or services, including those that involve an ongoing relationship with us or our partners. If you refuse to provide us with the information we require or later withdraw your consent to use and disclose this information, we may no longer be able to provide you with these products or services.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy and to our information gathering and dissemination practices. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, which we may do at any time without notice to you, we will post those changes on this page. We suggest that you periodically check the site for changes to this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy has an effective date of September 10th, 2018.

#### Get started with SlickText today!

##### We're here to help you through anything you need to get started.

#### You're in excellent hands. We work with some of the world's greatest companies.
